Okay, don't take this the wrong way, but, um,
好的，别误会，但是，呃，
you guys look... [sniffs]
你们看起来... [嗅了嗅]
and smell like garbage.
而且闻起来像垃圾。
Oh, there's an explanation.
哦，有个解释。
We just came from the doctor's office.
我们刚从医生办公室过来。
Today was our yearly checkup.
今天是我们的年度体检。
Oh. That makes sense.
哦。那就说得通了。
No, it doesn't.
不，这说不通。
How does going to the doctor end up like... this?
去看医生怎么会变成...这样？
Well, in order to really understand,
嗯，要真正理解，
we need to take you back to when we were five.
我们需要带你回到我们五岁的时候。
We were on the way to the doctor's office when we saw the most beautiful thing we ever seen.
我们正前往医生的办公室，就在那时我们看到了有史以来最美丽的东西。
[angelic chorus]
[天使合唱]
[kids] Cookie tower.
[孩子们] 饼干塔。
- Looks good, doesn't it?
看起来不错，不是吗？
[kids] Cookie tower.
[孩子们] 饼干塔。
We know going to the doctor's office has always been a challenge for you guys.
我们知道去医生办公室对你们来说一直是个挑战。
And us.
对我们也是。
So how about we make you a deal?
那我们做个交易怎么样？
[kids] Cookie tower.
[孩子们] 饼干塔。
He told us if we made it through that doctor's visit without any incidents, they'd buy us the cookie tower.
他说如果我们能顺利完成那次医生访问而没有任何意外，他们就会给我们买那个饼干塔。
Ooh, how'd it taste?
哦，味道怎么样？
We don't know. Five years, five disasters,
我们不知道。五年，五次灾难，
and five doctors later, we still haven't tasted the sweet,
和五位医生之后，我们仍然没有尝到那甜美的，
sugary goodness of the cookie tower.
糖分满满的饼干塔的美味。
[angelic chorus]
（天使合唱）
Would you guys stop doing that?
你们能不能别再那样做了？
Sorry.
对不起。
Wait, so you've been banned from five doctors?
等等，所以你们被五位医生禁止了？
Oh, we've been banned from almost every doctor in town.
哦，我们几乎被镇上所有的医生禁止了。
Dentists, podiatrists, we've even been banned
牙医、足病医生，我们甚至被
from Dr. Waffles.
华夫饼医生禁止了。
What is that, like, a breakfast place?
那是什么，像是一家早餐店吗？
No, she's a veterinarian.
不，她是一位兽医。
But she does put out those really dry, bone-shaped donuts.
但她确实会提供那些非常干的骨头形状甜甜圈。
Good thing she also puts out a fresh bowl of water.
好在她还会提供一碗新鲜的水。
We're no longer welcome there.
我们不再受欢迎了。
But this year, no crazy freak-outs
但今年，不会再有疯狂的失控
were gonna get in our way.
我们会克服一切困难。
We've each had our issues, but this time, we also had a plan.
我们每个人都有自己的问题，但这次，我们也有了一个计划。
Step forward and state your problem.
上前陈述你的问题。
Every time we go to the doctor's office,
每次我们去医生办公室，
I read the medical pamphlets, get convinced I have
我都会读那些医疗小册子，然后深信自己得了
all the diseases, and freak out.
所有疾病，接着就恐慌发作。
Solution?
解决办法？
Tablet full of vampire books to distract me.
用一整平板电脑的吸血鬼书籍来分散我的注意力。
Vampires live forever and never catch diseases.
吸血鬼永生不死，也不会得病。
Next?
下一个？
Doctors offices are the center of the evil germ universe.
医生办公室是邪恶细菌宇宙的中心。
Solution?
解决办法？
My antibacterial super-cape.
我的抗菌超级斗篷。
No evil germs are getting past this flu-fighting fabric.
没有邪恶的细菌能穿过这防流感面料。
Next?
下一个？
I have shy kidneys.
我的肾脏很害羞。
When the nurse gives me that little cup to fill,
当护士给我那个小杯子让我装满时，
I get a drought in my spout.
我的出口就干涸了。
Solution?
解决方案？
I pre-peed, so I'm pee-pared.
我提前尿了，所以我准备好了。
Hey, I drink out of that!
嘿，我喝那个的！
That's okay. I washed it out first.
没关系。我先洗过了。
Next?
下一步？
State your problem.
陈述你的问题。
We have four kids.
我们有四个孩子。
And we are about to see the last good doctor within 50 miles
而我们即将见到方圆50英里内
that hasn't banned us.
最后一个没有禁止我们的好医生。
Solution?
解决方案？
Relax, breathe, and make everyone believe
放松，深呼吸，让每个人都相信
we are the perfect model family.
我们是完美的模范家庭。
Even if we have to make believe.
即使我们必须假装。
Sorry, Anne.
对不起，安妮。
Ricky said he was too busy to teach me how to tie a tie.
Ricky说他太忙了，没时间教我怎么打领带。
Stupid homework.
愚蠢的作业。
What about you, honey?
你呢，亲爱的？
I have a little fear of needles.
我对针有点恐惧。
A little?
有点？
Last year, you scissor-kicked the doctor, stiff-armed a nurse,
去年，你用剪刀脚踢了医生，用胳膊肘顶了护士，
pushed a toddler off a wooden pony and used it
把一个小孩从木马上推下来，然后骑上它
as your getaway horse.
作为你的逃跑马。
I would have gotten away clean
我本可以干净利落地逃脱的
if that horse wasn't afraid of stairs.
如果不是那匹马害怕楼梯的话。
Solution?
解决方案？
Since there are no shots scheduled this year,
既然今年没有安排打针，
I'll be fine.
我会没事的。
Trust me, nothing's gonna go wrong this time.
相信我，这次不会出任何问题。
[chuckles]
[轻笑]
You gotta make time for me, Ricky!
你得抽时间陪我，Ricky！
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
[man] [whistling melody]
[rhythmic clapping] ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一、二、三、四！ ♪
[man] [whistling melody]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
♪ 呐、呐、呐、呐、呐呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na ♪
♪ 一、二 ♪ ♪ 呐、呐、呐 ♪
[man] ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一、二、三、四！ ♪
So we had our plan, and it was all going great
所以我们有了计划，一切都进行得很顺利
until we walked in the waiting room.
直到我们走进了候诊室。
Don't look at the pamphlets, don't look at the pamphlets,
别看那些小册子，别看那些小册子，
don't look at the pamphlets-- I gotta look at the pamphlets!
不要看那些小册子——我得看看那些小册子！
Mumps?
腮腺炎？
Why did I look at the pamphlets? - Okay, stay on target.
我为什么要看那些小册子？ - 好吧，保持专注。
Smiles, everybody, okay? Smiles.
大家微笑，好吗？微笑。
- Hello, uh, Andrea. - It's An-DRE-a.
- 你好，呃，安德莉亚。 - 是安-德-莉亚。
There's an accent over the "e."
“e”上面有个重音符号。
Ooh, were your parents French?
哦，你父母是法国人吗？
Why, do you have something against the French?
为什么，你对法国人有偏见吗？
No, no, no, no, no, not at all.
不，不，不，不，不，完全没有。
In fact, we are part French. We are the "Harpairs."
事实上，我们也有法国血统。我们是“哈帕伊尔”。
- Well in that case, avez-vous un rendez-vous? - Huh?
- 那么在这种情况下，您有预约吗？- 啊？
I asked if you had an appointment.
我问你有没有预约。
Ooh, ah--yes. I mean, oui.
哦，啊--是的。我是说，是的。
Wee-wee.
呃，呃。
Anyway, we're all here.
总之，我们都到齐了。
- Minus my husband, who's parking. What is taking him so long? - Okay, breathe. Relax.
- 除了我丈夫，他在停车。他怎么这么久？- 好的，深呼吸。放松。
- Model family. - Right, okay.
- 模范家庭。- 对，好的。
So, will the wait be long?
那么，等待时间会很长吗？
Well, we're running a bit behind.
嗯，我们有点落后了。
One of our doctors went home with the flu.
我们的一位医生因为流感回家了。
The flu? It's here?
流感？它在这里吗？
It's all around us. They even have pamphlets on it!
它无处不在。他们甚至有关于它的宣传册！
- Uh, and we're gonna wait over here.
- 呃，我们会在那边等待。
- Try go get us in there quick. - Okay.
- 尽量让我们快点进去。 - 好的。
Okay. [clears throat]
好的。[清嗓子]
Andrea, I don't mean to be pushy,
Andrea，我不是想催促，
but asking these four kids to wait can get a little tricky.
但让这四个孩子等待可能会有些棘手。
Are you asking for special treatment?
你是在要求特殊待遇吗？
No! No, no, no. Not at all.
不！不，不，不。完全不是。
But is that something that is available to, say, moi?
但那是可以提供给，比如说，我吗？
And--and what is with the sticker switch there?
还有——那里的贴纸是怎么回事？
[phone rings]
[电话铃响]
Dr. Miller's office.
米勒医生的办公室。
- Wha--what do the different colors mean? - Mrs. Harper, please.
- 什——不同颜色代表什么？ - 请哈珀太太接电话。
Okay, just where I'm from, green is good and red is bad
好的，只是在我家乡，绿色代表好，红色代表不好
and I see myself as more of a green.
而我自认为是绿色的。
Yes, a lot of very difficult cases today.
是的，今天有很多非常棘手的病例。
Am--am I a difficult case? Is that what red means?
我——我是个棘手的病例吗？红色是这个意思吗？
Okay, guys, focus. The cookie tower is in sight.
好了，伙计们，集中注意力。饼干塔就在眼前。
Solutions ready?
解决方案准备好了吗？
[boys] Ready.
准备好了。
[wheels squeaking]
（轮子吱吱作响）
Is that a--
那是——
It couldn't be a--
不可能是——
It is a!
是！
[all scream]
（所有人尖叫）
Oh, no.
哦，不。
[all] Oh, no.
（所有人）哦，不。
So the painters were moving a skeleton?
所以画家们在移动一具骷髅？
It was an educational skeleton.
那是一具教育用的骷髅。
His name is Boney Tony.
他的名字是Boney Tony。
Even worse than that skeleton-- they put us in separate rooms,
比那骷髅更糟糕的是——他们把我们分在不同的房间，
so I couldn't help my brothers.
所以我无法帮助我的兄弟们。
No pamphlets.
没有宣传册。
[heartbeat thumping]
[Ricky] Ah!
Good morning, I'm Dr. Miller.
早上好，我是Miller医生。
And, uh, who do we have here?
那么，我们这里是谁呢？
Dawn Harper. 10, healthy, active,
Dawn Harper。10岁，健康，活跃，
love soccer, no allergies, not my year for shots.
热爱足球，无过敏，今年不用打针。
Are we done?
我们结束了吗？
Done? We haven't even started your exam yet.
结束？我们还没开始给你做检查呢。
Great! So, what do you want to start with?
太好了！那你想从什么开始？
Blood pressure?
血压？
She's just trying to move things along
她只是想加快进度
so you can go see her brothers.
这样你就可以去看她的兄弟们了。
Always thinking of other people.
总是想着别人。
That's how we Harpers are-- the perfect model family.
这就是我们哈珀家——完美的模范家庭。
So, uh, new patient, huh? What brought you to our office?
那么，新病人，是吧？是什么让你来到我们办公室的？
Well, it's not because you're the last doctor
嗯，并不是因为你是方圆50英里内最后一个医生，如果你这么想的话。
within 50 miles, if that's what you're thinking.
在50英里范围内，如果这是你在想的。
- Why would I think that? - Pfft!
- 我为什么会那样想？ - 哼！
Ooh, red sticker. That's never fun.
哦，红色标签。那从来都不是好事。
- I knew it. - Okay, Mom.
- 我就知道。 - 好吧，妈妈。
- Too much pressure. - Tell me about it.
- 压力太大了。 - 说得太对了。
- I need your father. - No, I'm serious.
- 我需要你爸爸。 - 不，我是认真的。
Tom, I need you, where are you?
汤姆，我需要你，你在哪儿？
[air hissing]
[空气嘶嘶声]
Still looking for parking, Anne! It's a jungle out here!
还在找停车位，安妮！这里简直是个丛林！
The stupid mattress truck is taking up half the spots!
那该死的床垫卡车占了一半的停车位！
I mean, do you really need that many spots?
我是说，你真的需要那么多车位吗？
All right, all right. I think this guy's leaving.
好吧，好吧。我觉得这家伙要走了。
Come on, buddy, back out.
快点，伙计，倒车。
Back out, back out, back-- oh, he's pulling back in, Anne.
倒车，倒车，倒——哦，他又开回来了，安妮。
Why? Why are you pulling back in?
为什么？你为什么要开回来？
No! Life is so unfair!
不！生活真不公平！
Ooh, he's pulling back out again.
哦，他又开始倒出来了。
Great, great, take it and get up here, now!
太好了，太好了，开上来，现在就上来！
"Physician parking only."
仅供医生停车。
Only when?
只有什么时候？
Only when your wife is yelling at you?
只有当你妻子在对你大吼大叫的时候吗？
Works for me.
对我来说挺管用的。
So after I got through my exam, I blew up a latex glove
所以我在考完试后，吹起了一个乳胶手套
and made a little turkey.
并做了一只小火鸡。
[mimics turkey gobbling]
[模仿火鸡咯咯叫]
What?
什么？
Everyone deals with stress in their own way.
每个人应对压力的方式都不同。
Anyway, Mom went to go help Ricky and Dicky
总之，妈妈去帮里基和迪基了
while I went to go help Nicky battle the evil germs.
而我则去帮尼基对抗那些邪恶的细菌。
Better?
好些了吗？
It could use a cape.
也许它需要个披风。
[sighs]
［叹气］
Ah, yes.
啊，是的。
Thank you very much, Cunninghams.
非常感谢你们，卡unninghams一家。
- Mom? - [screams]
- 妈妈？- ［尖叫］
Oh! Oh, my gosh.
哦！我的天哪。
Sorry. How's Nicky?
对不起。Nicky怎么样了？
Cookie tower, here we come.
饼干塔，我们来了。
How's your sticker problem?
你的贴纸问题解决了吗？
Hmm.
嗯。
Great work. I'm off to see the whizzer.
干得好。我要去看旋转器了。
- Those. - Ahh.
- 那些。 - 啊。
This place is a madhouse today.
今天这里简直是个疯人院。
I thought you called in a replacement doctor.
我以为你叫了替补医生。
I did. Dr. Fetoosh was supposed to be here,
我是叫了。费图什医生本该在这里，
but he's running late.
但他迟到了。
I can't wait to meet him. I hear he's quite the character.
我迫不及待想见他。听说他是个很有个性的人。
Hey, hon. Sorry I'm late.
嘿，亲爱的。抱歉我迟到了。
Good thing that physician spot was open,
好在那个医生位置空着，
so just call me Doctor.
所以就叫我医生吧。
That's it! Ah, doctor!
就是这样！啊，医生！
- You're Dr. Fetoosh. - I am?
- 你是Fetoosh医生。 - 我是吗？
Yes, and you're quite the character.
是的，你真是个有趣的人。
Ooh.
哦。
Wait, why am I doing this again?
等等，我为什么要这么做？
They red-stickered our files, Tom.
他们用红标标记了我们的文件，汤姆。
I'm no doctor, but that can't be good.
我不是医生，但这肯定不是好事。
You are a doctor,
你是一位医生，
which means you have access to the files.
这意味着你可以访问那些文件。
And if we don't change the red sticker on that file to green,
如果我们不把那份文件上的红标改成绿标，
they'll never let us bring the kids back here.
他们永远不会让我们把孩子带回这里。
Well, then, the doctor is in.
那么，医生来了。
Oh!
哦！
Oh! [laughs] Oh, Dr. Fetoosh.
哦！[笑] 哦，费图什医生。
- You are such a character. - Ahh.
- 你真是个有趣的人。 - 啊。
- Lovely meeting you. - Oh.
- 很高兴见到你。 - 哦。
Dr. Fetoosh, you're here. Nice tie.
费图什医生，你来了。领带不错。
The kids are gonna love that!
孩子们会喜欢的！
Oh! [laughs]
哦！[笑]
I did that on purpose... 'cause I am Dr. Fetoosh.
我故意这么做的...因为我就是费图什医生。
And I am quite the character.
我确实是个有趣的角色。
Oh, is that the, uh... the, uh, Harper file?
哦，那是，呃... 那个，呃，哈珀的文件吗？
Yes, but let's start you off with something easier.
是的，但让我们先从简单的事情开始。
[baby cries]
[婴儿哭泣]
Oh, that is a real baby!
哦，那是个真宝宝！
Dicky? Anything happening in there?
迪基？里面有什么动静吗？
[Dicky] No, my lemonade stand is closed for business.
[迪基] 没有，我的柠檬水摊已经歇业了。
You know I'm not really talking about lemonade, right?
你知道我不是真的在说柠檬水，对吧？
I know.
我知道。
Okay, do you need me to sing the pee-pee song that Mom always used to sing?
好吧，你需要我唱妈妈总是唱的那个尿尿歌吗？
Oh, that'd be nice.
哦，那会很好。
♪ Raindrops and waterfalls the deep blue sea ♪
♪ 雨滴和瀑布 ♪ ♪ 深蓝的大海 ♪
♪ These are the things that help us go-- ♪
♪ 这些都是帮助我们前进的事物 ♪
[Dicky] It's not working!
这不管用！
Okay, Dicky, calm down.
好的，Dicky，冷静下来。
I'm gonna get you through this, trust me.
我会帮你度过这个难关，相信我。
Nothing's gonna stop us from getting that cookie tower.
没有什么能阻止我们拿到那个饼干塔。
I'm pregnant!
我怀孕了！
- What? - I'm pregnant!
- 什么？ - 我怀孕了！
- You're not pregnant. - Wait, who's pregnant?
- 你没怀孕。 - 等等，谁怀孕了？
- Me. - Congratulations!
- 我。 - 恭喜你！
He's not pregnant, he just read a pamphlet.
他没怀孕，他只是读了一本小册子。
- Give me that. - Easy, Dawn, I'm with child.
- 给我那个。 - 别急，Dawn，我怀孕了。
- You're not with child. - I'm gonna be an uncle!
- 你没怀孕。 - 我要当舅舅了！
You're not gonna be an uncle!
你不会当舅舅的！
Then who's gonna teach the little guy how to ride a bike?
那谁来教小家伙骑自行车？
Okay, you go in there and get your lemonade stand open.
好吧，你进去把你的柠檬水摊开张。
- You know it's really not lem-- - Just get in there!
- 你知道那真的不是柠—— - 快进去！
You come with me!
你跟我来！
Calm down, Ricky. You're not pregnant.
冷静点，Ricky。你没怀孕。
Then why am I so moody and nauseous?
I think it's the morning sickness.
Ricky, you're a boy.
You're right. I'm a boy.
It's scientifically impossible.
- Ow! - What?
- I think it just kicked. - You're not pregnant!
Okay, here, just focus on the adorable puppy magazine.
I'm gonna go back and check on Dicky.
Oh, and Mom said to take this in case any of us
got nervous stomachs.
如果有人胃不舒服就吃这个。
Ew, chalky.
呃，口感像石灰。
[Ricky voice-over] All right, puppies, calm me down.
[Ricky 旁白] 好了，小狗们，让我冷静下来。
Interesting.
有意思。
Puppies can get rabies. Huh?
小狗会得狂犬病。嗯？
People can get rabies. People can get rabies?
人也会得狂犬病。人也会得狂犬病？
One of the symptoms is foaming at the mouth!
其中一个症状是口吐白沫！
I'm foaming at the mouth!
我在口吐白沫！
I never want to see anything like that again.
我再也不想看到那样的东西了。
Here you go, Dr. Fetoosh.
给你，Fetoosh医生。
Your next patient is Ricky Harper.
您的下一位病人是Ricky Harper。
Uh, where's the rest of the file?
呃，文件的其他部分在哪里？
Oh, his entire medical history is in there.
哦，他的全部医疗记录都在里面。
No, I'm talking about the important part.
不，我说的是重要的部分。
You know, where the sticker is.
你知道，就是贴纸的地方。
You know, you can tell a lot about a patient
你知道，通过贴纸的颜色可以了解很多关于病人的信息。
by the color of his sticker.
你真是个有趣的人，Fetoosh医生。
You're such a character, Dr. Fetoosh.
是的，我知道。我真的需要那份文件。
Yes, I know. I really need that file.
我有狂犬病！
- I have rabies! - He--he has rabies!
他...他有狂犬病！
He has rabies!
他得了狂犬病！
Who has rabies?
谁得了狂犬病？
Nicky?
尼基？
We've gotta get out of here!
我们得离开这里！
Someone has... rabies!
有人得了...狂犬病！
I did it!
我做到了！
- Rabies! - Nicky!
狂犬病！
No! My precious!
尼基！
- Help me! - [screams]
不！我的宝贝！
Ah!
救我！
- Nicky! - Stay away from me!
Nicky! 离我远点！
- Get back in here! - No!
回到这里来！ 不！
- He's got rabies! - There's no rabies.
他有狂犬病！ 没有狂犬病。
Come here.
过来。
- Ow! - What about Ricky?
哎哟！ Ricky呢？
Don't be ridiculous. He doesn't have rabies.
别荒谬了。他没有狂犬病。
He's having babies.
他要生孩子了。
Okay, neither of those things are happening.
好吧，这两件事都没发生。
He just took some tablets for his stomach
他只是吃了一些治胃的药
that made his mouth foam up.
让他的嘴起泡沫了。
Huh, that makes more sense.
嗯，这样解释就合理多了。
But there's still germs out there.
但外面还是有细菌的。
You know what else is out there?
你知道外面还有什么吗？
A delicious dream with our names on it.
还有一个属于我们的美梦。
Now, we may have lost our tablet, our cape,
现在，我们可能丢了药片，丢了斗篷，
and my favorite water bottle...
还有我最喜欢的水瓶……
but there's one thing we haven't lost...
但我们没有失去一样东西……
our burning love of cookies.
我们对饼干的热爱。
So, Nicky, I have just two words for you.
所以，尼基，我只有两个字给你。
[chanting] Cookie tower.
饼干塔。
[all chanting] Cookie tower, cookie tower,
[所有人齐声] 饼干塔，饼干塔，
cookie tower, cookie tower!
饼干塔，饼干塔！
So the power of the tower helped Nicky
于是，塔的力量帮助尼基
get through his exam...
通过了考试...
[kids chanting] Cookie tower, cookie tower,
[孩子们齐声] 饼干塔，饼干塔，
cookie tower.
饼干塔。
- You're good to go. [kids cheering]
- 你可以走了。[孩子们欢呼]
[Dawn] And got Ricky through his.
[Dawn] 也让瑞奇通过了。
[kids chanting] Cookie tower, cookie tower,
[孩子们齐声] 饼干塔，饼干塔，
cookie tower.
饼干塔。
[both] Yes!
是的！
And even got Dicky back on track.
甚至让Dicky重新回到了正轨。
[kids chanting] Cookie tower, cookie tower,
孩子们唱着：饼干塔，饼干塔，
cookie tower, cookie tower...
饼干塔，饼干塔...
[Dicky] Yes! I'm filling it!
Dicky：是的！我在填满它！
[kids chanting] Cookie tower...
孩子们唱着：饼干塔...
[Dicky] A little too much.
Dicky：有点太多了。
I can't stop! I need more cups!
我停不下来！我需要更多杯子！
Stop chanting! Stop chanting!
别唱了！别唱了！
Just use the toilet.
就用厕所吧。
[Dicky] Oh.
哦。
- Okay, Dicky, you're all set. [kids cheering]
好的，Dicky，你准备好了。[孩子们欢呼]
- We all passed. - The cookie tower is ours!
我们都通过了。- 饼干塔是我们的了！
Yes! Woo-hoo!
太好了！哇呼！
Wait, honey, what happened to your hand?
等等，亲爱的，你的手怎么了？
Oh, it's nothing.
哦，没什么。
Just a little cut from a nail outside the window.
只是窗外钉子划破了一点。
A nail? Hmm.
钉子？嗯。
Looks like you may need a tetanus shot.
看起来你可能需要打一针破伤风。
A shot?
打针？
But--but I'm not supposed to have a shot.
但是——但是我本来不应该打针的。
There are no shots this year.
今年没有打针。
Don't worry, it won't hurt.
别担心，不会疼的。
Okay, relax. I can totally do this.
好的，放松。我完全可以做到。
I'm fine.
我没事。
She's getting on the wooden horse!
她要上木马了！
- What happ-- - Oh, I'm sorry!
怎么了——哦，对不起！
No, I, um-- Oh!
不，我，呃——哦！
- Dawn, come on. You're being ridiculous.
Dawn，拜托。你太夸张了。
It's one little shot.
就一个小小的针。
[chanting] Cookie tower.
[吟唱] 饼干塔。
[boys chanting] Cookie tower, cookie tower-- - That's not gonna work on me.
[男孩们吟唱] 饼干塔，饼干塔-- - 这对我没用。
Dawn, come on, you were the one who rallied us.
黎明，拜托，是你把我们召集起来的。
Yeah, if it weren't for you,
是啊，如果不是你，
none of us would have gotten through our exams.
我们谁也不会通过考试。
Yeah, and since you helped us get over our fears,
是的，既然你帮我们克服了恐惧，
let us help you get over yours.
让我们帮你克服你的恐惧。
Aw, guys, that's so sweet. Not gonna work either.
哦，伙计们，这太贴心了。也没用。
We thought you'd say that.
我们猜你会这么说。
So... get her!
所以... 抓住她！
[all] Whoa!
哇！
Dawn, what did you do?
Dawn，你做了什么？
I don't know how to work this thing!
我不知道怎么操作这东西！
Here! Let me do it.
给我，我来弄。
Uh-oh.
哎呀。
Now what are we gonna do?
我们现在该怎么办？
There's no way to get back in the window.
没办法从窗户回去了。
Looks like there's only one way off this thing.
看来只有一条路能离开这东西了。
You want me to jump into a germ-infested dumpster?
你要我跳进一个满是细菌的垃圾桶？
Without a cape?
没有披风？
No, onto the back of that mattress truck.
不，跳到那辆装着床垫的卡车后面。
- Better, but, nope. - Me neither.
- 更好，但，不行。 - 我也是。
- No way. - Come on, guys.
- 不可能。 - 拜托，伙计们。
I'll make you a deal.
我给你们做个交易。
If we do this together,
如果我们一起做这件事，
I'll go back in there and get that shot.
我会回去那里拿到那张照片。
[boys] Deal.
[男孩们] 成交。
Okay, on the count of three,
好的，数到三，
I'm gonna pull this pin, and out we go.
我会拔掉这个插销，我们就出发。
One, two...
一，二...
- three! [all scream]
三！[所有人尖叫]
So that's why you're covered in garbage.
所以这就是你浑身是垃圾的原因。
Yep.
是的。
After falling into a dumpster, getting a shot was no big deal.
掉进垃圾桶后，拍张照片不算什么大事。
But if everything worked out, where is this cookie tower?
但如果一切顺利，这个饼干塔在哪里？
Well, not everything worked out.
嗯，并非一切都顺利。
Dad still hadn't gotten the folder, but Mom had a plan.
爸爸还没拿到文件夹，但妈妈有个计划。
So he says, "Doctor, I need a second opinion."
于是他说：“医生，我需要第二个意见。”
So I say, "You're ugly too."
于是我说：“你也挺丑的。”
[laughter]
[笑声]
Oh, it's good to be a doctor.
哦，当医生真好。
[whispers] Yes! Take that, Andrea.
是的！让安德莉亚看看。
Come on, let's go.
快点，我们走吧。
Oh! Oh, I'm sorry.
哦！哦，对不起。
So sorry I'm late.
非常抱歉我迟到了。
There was a broken down mattress truck, and some jerk
有一辆坏掉的床垫卡车，还有个混蛋
parked his minivan in my physician's spot.
把他的小型货车停在我的医生车位上。
I'm sorry, who are you?
对不起，你是谁？
I'm Dr. Fetoosh.
我是费图什医生。
What do you mean? He's Dr. Fetoosh.
你什么意思？他是费图什医生。
- And he's quite the character. - I am.
- 他真是个有趣的人物。 - 确实如此。
No, I'm Dr. Fetoosh, and I'm quite the character.
不，我是Fetoosh医生，我确实是个有趣的人物。
Do your tie thing, Doctor.
医生，展示你的领带技巧吧。
Oh, oh, of course.
哦，哦，当然。
The kids love it.
孩子们喜欢这个。
No, the kids love this.
不，孩子们喜欢的是这个。
You're not a doctor, are you?
你不是医生，对吧？
Well, according to my parking space, I am.
嗯，根据我的停车位来看，我是医生。
Get out.
出去。
Oh, um, you should double-check the Jarvis baby.
哦，嗯，你应该再检查一下Jarvis家的宝宝。
- Wow.
哇。
Hey, we're back. Um, do you validate parking?
嘿，我们回来了。嗯，你们提供停车优惠吗？
Unbelievable.
难以置信。
So this is just a validation sticker?
所以这只是一张验证贴纸？
Yes, green one's for under an hour,
是的，绿色的适用于一小时以内，
red's for anything longer than an hour.
红色的适用于超过一小时。
[both] Ohhhh.
哦。
So for the sixth year in a row,
所以连续第六年，
we were banned from a doctor's office.
我们被禁止进入医生的办公室。
But since Mom and Dad are why we're never allowed back,
但由于是爸爸妈妈的原因我们不被允许回来，
technically it wasn't our fault.
从技术上讲，这不是我们的错。
Which is why we finally get...
这就是为什么我们终于可以...
That!
那个！
[kids mimic angelic chorus singing]
[孩子们模仿天使合唱团的歌声]
Oh, this is awesome!
哦，这太棒了！
And we don't have to go to the doctor for another year.
而且我们明年才需要再去医生那里。
- [sneezes] - [sneezes]
- [打喷嚏] - [打喷嚏]
- [sneezes] - Oh, no.
- [打喷嚏] - 哦，不。
This looks like a job for Dr. Fetoosh.
看来这得请费图什医生出马了。
I'll go get him.
我去叫他。
- Look at these, guys. - Oh, my gosh.
- 看看这些，伙计们。 - 哦，天哪。
[all talking over one another]
[所有人同时说话]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
[whistling melody]
[口哨旋律]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪